socialinterview.com 2013-09-27

# Social Interview Privacy Policy

5 August 2011

Privacy Policy (General - Facebook Applications)

Last modified: 5 August 2011

At Onoko International Limited ("Onoko") , we value your privacy, and have crafted this Privacy Policy to help you understand how we collect and use the information that you choose to give us about yourself.

Specifically, this Privacy Policy covers how Onoko collects and uses the information that you choose to give us that personally identifies you, such as your name, email address, or other data which can be reasonably linked to such information by Onoko("Personal Information").

This Privacy Policy generally applies to all products, services or websites offered by Onoko or its subsidiaries built on the Facebook Platform ("Products").  If a specific Product collects additional data, or uses it in a way different to our other Products, we will notify you by providing a link to the relevant modifications in the terms of use for that Product.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy please contact us at privacy@onokointernational.com or write to us at:

622-623 Topsail Plaza,

11 On Sum Street,

Shek Mun, Shatin,

New Territories

1.        Information Onoko collects

When you use an Onoko Product we will collect and use the following types of Personal Information which you have already provided to Facebook:

  1. Basic Information - your name, profile picture, gender, networks, user ID, list of friends, and any other information you have shared with everyone via Facebook.

  2. Specific Information \- any Personal Information that you specifically choose to share with Onoko when you sign up for a Product.  This will be specifically identified on the "Request for Permissions" screen that forms part of the sign up process for the Product.

As you use the Product, Onoko will also collect and use the following types of information:

  3. Usage Information \- anonymous information about user behaviour, including, for example: your internet protocol address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, and the date and time.

  4. User Generated Content \- while using the Product, you may be invited to interact with other users of the Product, write comments, or otherwise provide information.

  5. Activity Information \- we may record anonymous data about your use of the site,  ("Activity Information"). This information is used for internal analytics, the results of which are used to improve the application.

2.        How Onoko uses your information

Any information which you have chosen to give us may be stored indefinitely on our servers, or on a database controlled by Facebook.

Onoko will use your Personal Information as follows:

  1. to provide you with a better experience and improve the quality of our Products.  For example, we will use this Personal Information to customise your experience of the Product to provide you with content relevant to your location, language, gender, friends, or other characteristics.

  2. to provide you with advertising content that is relevant to your characteristics.  In doing so no Personal Information will passed to third parties or advertisers.

  3. to feed information into our Products for you to edit and then re-post to Facebook or share with your friends. Onoko itself doesn't use, view or modify this information, we just automatically pass it on to our Product for you to use.

  4. to provide you with relevant content updates or recommendations.  You will be able to opt out of any content updates or recommendations if you don't want to receive them.

In addition to the above, we may use the information we collect to:

  1. Provide, maintain, protect, and improve our Products and develop new Products; and

  2. Protect the rights or property of Onoko or our users.

If we use your Personal Information in a manner other than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent before such use.

Onoko processes Personal Information on our servers in Hong Kong and in other countries, and will take all practicable steps to secure your Personal Information from unauthorized use.

3.        Enforcement and your rights

Onoko complies with the Hong Kong Personal Data Protection Ordinance (Cap. 486) ("HKPDPO") and will handle your Personal Information in compliance with the requirements of the HKDPO.

Under the HKPDPO you have a right to request access to, and correction of, your Personal Information.  If you wish to exercise this right at any time, please make the request in accordance with the procedures specified in the HKPDPO and address it to [Mr. Janakan Arulkumarasan] at Onoko's address listed above.

Please note that if you choose to exercise this right Onoko will charge a reasonable administrative fee to cover the handling of your request, and may defer processing your request until receipt of this fee.

In addition to the protections provided by the HKPDPO, when Onoko receives a formal written complaint, Onoko's policy is to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns to resolve any complaints. 

4.        Changes to this Privacy Policy

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. Onoko will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent.  We will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice either when you next access the Product, or by way of email.  We will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.

5.        Sales or Transfers of Products

Onoko may sell Products to a third party for business reasons.  If this occurs, the third party will gain access to your Personal Information.  In this event, Onoko will provide you with notification of the sale either when you next use the Product, or by way of email.
